# Osipov Yuri

Yaroslavl, Russia (+7)9201331243 – yuraosipov<br/>2012@gmail.com

## Education

Self taught developer

## Experience

Period	Company	Position	Responsibilities
September 2016 – Present time	Startup	Lead Developer and Server administrator	Development of custom scripts for gaming needs; Maintaining the stability of the server; Full configuration of the physical machine (Assembly, software installation);
June 2021 – march 2022	LLC Sevserstal	Developer	Development of robots in VBA and Python to improve the company's internal business processes
march 2022 – july 2022	LLC Pikta	Senior Developer	Development of robots in VBA and Python to improve the company's internal business processes

## Programming skills

Languages	Databases	Tools and Technologies
Python; C++; C; Lua; VB.Net; C#; SQL; Django	SQLite; MySQL	Vim; Linux; Git; Jira; MarkDown;

### Other Skills

Languages: Russian (Native); English (between Advanced and Proficient).

### About me

I'm a software developer with more than 5 years experience of work using different technologies including C, C++, Python(Many modules including requests, asyncio, python-valve etc), Lua and many more.

I'm a big fan of unix based operating systems, my favorite linux distro is Fedora with Gnome DE.

I have a lot of experience in server administration of linux and windows servers. I do it for almost 6 years as of now. I've started from game servers and moved on to more complicated projects.

For now I'm open to job offers, I'm looking for something that I will enjoy doing, such as game development or backend development. I'm always ready to learn new technologies and to extend my field of view.

My goal for 2022 is to learn Rust and find an opportunity to use it in some interesting project.

PDF version